<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on DevSetGo</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on DevSetGo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 17:57:50 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Work</title>
      <link>/articles/2018/2018-12-26-current-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 23:16:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/2018/2018-12-26-current-work/</guid>
      <description>Some interesting stuff I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading about or looking into.
 Flask Blueprints - I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading about flask blueprints and building a basic template to utilize. Need to add in a User management with Flask-Login and my template should be done. Kubernettes - This is the competitor to Docker Swarm. I will be using it at work. Still runs the docker enginer, but is supposed to be a better cluster management platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And We Are Back...</title>
      <link>/articles/2018/2018-12-26-and-we-are-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 22:39:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/2018/2018-12-26-and-we-are-back/</guid>
      <description>So I broke my last site (or two). I had been using Wordpress and decided I wanted something light weight. So I started playing with Ghost and eventually had it running on my Docker instance. Initially I had it setup to learn and test, while also using it as my blog. Then I ran into a lot of issues&amp;hellip; way more than you should run into when learning/building a blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flask Sufee Admin</title>
      <link>/projects/2018-12-26-flask-sufee-admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 18:30:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/2018-12-26-flask-sufee-admin/</guid>
      <description>Sufee HTML5 Admin Dashboard Template (for Flask!) Sufee is a responsive Bootstrap 4 Admin Template. It provides you with a collection of ready to use code snippets and utilities, custom pages, a collection of applications and some useful widgets. Preview of this awesome admin template available here: https://colorlib.com/polygon/sufee/index.html
 project forked to setup to use in a Flask project.  Demo Site: Here TOC  Built With Changelog Authors License  Built With  Flask Sass Bootstrap Chart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Camunda</title>
      <link>/projects/2018-12-26-learning-camunda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 18:29:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/2018-12-26-learning-camunda/</guid>
      <description>Camunda-BPM-Learning Project to store what I learn about Camunda and use for future base projects. Camunda BPM Documents (https://docs.camunda.org) - currently built on v7.9
ChangeLog
Find all Camunda related posts.
Things in the example As of 0.1.4  Accounts Receivable process with BPMN and DMN file for cost center routing Get current user when submitting form or approving Use of singleResult for getting 3 outputs from DMN (primary approver, limit, &amp;amp; secondary approver) Each step of the process has an embedded HTML form following basic bootstrap design Cam-Script to fetch varialbles and display on screen (embedded HTML forms)  As of 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pynote</title>
      <link>/projects/2018-12-26-pynote/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 18:29:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/2018-12-26-pynote/</guid>
      <description>Journal, Idea Tracker and Other things. This application is based and built off Flask-AppBuilder by dpgaspar
Running demo hosted at pynote.devsetgo.com * username Admin * password $Password
Run the application from OS Prerequisits * Python (3.5) * virtualenv
Run the application * create a virtual environment - virtualenv env * Install Requirements in Virtual Environment - pip install -r requirements.txt * fabmanger create-admin - Follow instructions * fabmanger Run - Application is now running - Test and modify code as you want</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me</title>
      <link>/about/me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 17:57:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/me/</guid>
      <description> A citizen of the USA and Ireland Tá Béarla agam, ach táim ag foghlaim na Gaeilge translate USAF veteran A geeky guy married to a nerdy girl I&amp;rsquo;m from Indianapolis, Indiana, but I call Florida home. USA allowfullscreen     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things I like....</title>
      <link>/about/like/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 17:57:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/like/</guid>
      <description>I like&amp;hellip;  Python - I think this is a beautiful language. JavaScript - because you are pretty much required to know it anymore! BPMN Tools like Camunda because I can build as fast as I think, then adapt quickly. Docker and I need to learn Kubernettes&amp;hellip;  and when I am required too&amp;hellip; * JAVA for work * .NET I used to use it (C# and VB.NET)
I should mention that I also love Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>